Guide to the Leonard S. Marcus Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- September 2015 Acquisition, circa 1850-2015; circa 1975-2015; 110.08; (98 boxes)
  - Writings, circa 1981-2015; 77.5; (68 boxes)
    - Books, circa 1983-2013
      - Minders of Make-Believe: Idealists, Entrepreneurs, and the Making of American Children's Literature, circa 1972-2007
        - Agents, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 743)
        - Editors, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 744-745)
        - Printers and designers, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 746)
        - Critics, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 747)
        - Pura Belpré, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 748)
        - Librarians, circa 1997-2007 (Box 33, Folder 749)
        - History chapters 4-6, circa 1997-2007 (Box 34, Folder 750)
        - Houghton history 19th century, circa 1997-2007 (Box 34, Folder 751-752)
        - Viking 75th anniversary essay, circa 1997-2007 (Box 34, Folder 753)
        - Parley's Magazine, Greenwood Press, circa 1997-2007 (Box 34, Folder 754)
        - New history book material, circa 1997-2007 (Box 34, Folder 755-756)
        - Quotes, epigraphs, etc., circa 1997-2007 (Box 34, Folder 757)
        - McLoughlin Brothers, circa 1997-2007 (Box 34, Folder 758)
        - Linda Lapides, Baltimore children's book history, circa 1997-2007 (Box 34, Folder 759)
        - Yale senior thesis, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 760)
        - Elizabeth Coatsworth Papers, University of New England, circa 1997-2007 (Box 34, Folder 761)
        - Publishers Weekly 125th anniversary issue, 1997 (Box 34, Folder 762)
        - Harry Potter phenomenon, circa 1997-2007 (Box 34, Folder 763-764)
        - Weston Woods Institute, circa 1997-2007 (Box 34, Folder 765)
        - George Scheer, circa 1997-2007 (Box 34, Folder 766)
        - Columbia University oral history project, circa 1997-2007 (Box 34, Folder 767)
        - Cartoons about children's literature, circa 1997-2007 (Box 34, Folder 768)
        - Chicago publishing, circa 1997-2007 (Box 34, Folder 769)
        - Bill Morris, circa 1997-2007 (Box 34, Folder 770)
        - 1930s Houghton history, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 771-774)
        - The Horn Book inaugural issue and Louise Seaman issue, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 775)
        - Publishers Weekly library, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 776)
        - 1920s history, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 777)
        - William Nicholson essay, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 778)
        - Minders of Make-Believe manuscript, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 779-782)
        - Publishers Weekly excerpt, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 783)
        - New York Public Library central children's room essay, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 784)
        - Minders of Make-Believe foreword, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 785)
        - Minders of Make-Believe acknowledgments, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 786)
        - Minders of Make-Believe reviews, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 787)
        - Cooperative Children's Book Center discussion of Minders of Make-Believe, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 788)
        - Minders of Make-Believe research, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 789)
        - Minders of Make-Believe letters from readers, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 790)
        - Louise Seaman Bechtel, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 791)
        - Letters at Simmons College, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 792)
        - Nonfiction history, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 793)
        - Horn Book archives at Simmons College, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 794)
        - Margaret Wise Brown Horn Book material, circa 1997-2007 (Box 35, Folder 795)
        - Library of Congress film tribute to Robert McCloskey, circa 1997-2007 (Box 36, Folder 796)
        - Research material, circa 1997-2007 (Box 36, Folder 797)
        - Morrow, circa 1997-2007 (Box 36, Folder 798-800)
      - Oscar: The Big Adventure of a Little Sock Monkey, circa 2005-2006
        - Oscar: The Big Adventure of a Little Sock Monkey, circa 2005-2006 (Box 51, Folder 1315)
      - Pass It Down: Five Picture-Book Families Make Their Mark, circa 2004-2006
        Also known as its working title All in the Family.
        - Pass It Down dummy, circa 2004-2006 (Box 37, Folder 807)
        - All in the Family manuscript, circa 2004-2006 (Box 37, Folder 808)
        - Pass It Down (copy edited), circa 2004-2006 (Box 37, Folder 809)
        - Pass It Down reviews, circa 2004-2006 (Box 37, Folder 810)
        - Pass It Down publicity, circa 2004-2006 (Box 37, Folder 811)
        - Pass It Down draft, circa 2004-2006 (Box 37, Folder 812)
        - All in the Family introduction, circa 2004-2006 (Box 37, Folder 813)
        - Pass It Down e-mail correspondence, circa 2004-2006 (Box 37, Folder 814)
        - Walker bibliography, circa 2004-2006 (Box 37, Folder 815)
        - Donald Crews, Ann Jonas, and Nina Crews, circa 2004-2006 (Box 37, Folder 816)
        - Thacher, Edith, and Clement Hurd, circa 2004-2006 (Box 37, Folder 817)
        - Walter Dean Myers and Christopher Myers, circa 2004-2006 (Box 37, Folder 818)
        - The Pinkneys, circa 2004-2006 (Box 37, Folder 819)
        - Anne and Lizzy Rockwell, circa 2004-2006 (Box 37, Folder 820)
        - Pass It Down captions and photo credits, circa 2004-2006 (Box 37, Folder 821)
        - Pass It Down promotion, circa 2006-2017 (Box 37, Folder 822)
        - Pass It Down proof, 2006 (Box 97 (Oversize), Folder 2316)
      - Randolph Caldecott: The Man Who Could Not Stop Drawing, circa 2011-2013
        - Houghton library research, 2012 (Box 38, Folder 839)
        - Amazon, Randolph Caldecott and Brian Selznick conversation, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 840)
        - Caldecott publicity and reviews, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 841)
        - The New York Times Book Review, Caldecott book, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 842)
        - Children and Libraries, Caldecott book, circa 2011-2013 (Box 38, Folder 843)
        - History of the Newbery and Caldecott medals, circa 2011-2013 (Box 38, Folder 844)
        - Randolph Caldecott: The Man Who Could Not Stop Drawing, circa 2011-2013 (Box 38, Folder 845)
        - Color layout, corrected, 2012-12-19 (Box 95 (Oversize), Folder 2311)
        - Color layout, corrected, 2012-09-19 (Box 95 (Oversize), Folder 2312)
        - Color layout, corrected, 2012-10-26 (Box 95 (Oversize), Folder 2313)
      - The Runaway Bunny: A 75th Anniversary Retrospective, 1999
        - The Runaway Bunny retrospective, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 604)
      - Show Me a Story: Why Picture Books Matter, circa 1988-2013
        Originally published as Ways of Telling: Conversations on the Art of the Picture Book.
        - Show Me a Story reviews and publicity, circa 2012-2013 (Box 39, Folder 868)
        - New Ways of Telling (Candlewick), circa 2011-2012 (Box 39, Folder 869-870)
        - Author photos for Ways of Telling, circa 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 871)
        - Dutton interview book headnotes, circa 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 872-873)
        - Dutton interview book new correspondence, final corrections, photo permissions, circa 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 874-875)
        - Ways of Telling publicity, reviews, letters, circa 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 876-876a)
        - Mitsumasa Anno interview and drawings, circa 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 877)
        - Ashley Bryan interview, circa 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 878)
        - Tana Hoban interview, circa 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 879)
        - New James Marshall interview (Dutton), circa 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 880)
        - Karla Kuskin interview, circa 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 881-882)
        - James Marshall interview, Publishers Weekly, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 883)
        - James Marshall transcript, circa 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 884)
        - Iona Opie interview, The Lion and the Unicorn, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 885-885a)
        - Rosemary Wells interview, circa 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 886)
        - Eric Carle Dutton interview, circa 2001-2002 (Box 39, Folder 887-888)
        - Eric Carle interview, circa 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 889)
        - Vera B. Williams, circa 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 890)
        - Maurice Sendak interviews, circa 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 891-892)
        - William Steig interview, circa 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 893)
        - Charlotte Zolotow interview, circa 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 894)
        - Iona Opie interview, circa 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 895)
        - Jerry Pinkney interview, circa 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 896)
        - Dutton interviews, circa 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 897)
        - Interview book proposal and correspondence, circa 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 898)
        - Mitsumasa Anno interview, circa 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 899)
        - Alvin Schwartz and Judith Gorog interview, circa 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 900)
      - Side by Side: Five Favorite Picture-Book Teams Go to Work, circa 2000-2007
        - Side by Side slides, 2007 (Box 17, Folder 428)
        - Side by Side color proofs, circa 2000-2007 (Box 41, Folder 910)
        - Sam and the Tigers, Side by Side, circa 2000-2007 (Box 41, Folder 911)
        - Side by Side reviews, circa 2001-2002 (Box 41, Folder 912)
        - Side by Side missing things, circa 2000-2001 (Box 41, Folder 913-914)
        - Side by Side publicity, circa 2001-2002 (Box 41, Folder 915)
        - Side by Side glossary, circa 2000-2001 (Box 41, Folder 916)
        - Research and author photos, circa 2000-2001 (Box 41, Folder 917-918)
        - Side by Side permission copies, circa 2000-2001 (Box 41, Folder 919)
        - The Magic School Bus Explores the Five Senses by Joanna Cole and Bruce Degen, circa 2000-2001 (Box 41, Folder 920)
        - The Stinky Cheese Man, circa 2000-2001 (Box 41, Folder 921)
        - Third Walker book, circa 2000-2001 (Box 41, Folder 922)
        - Side by Side introduction, circa 2000-2001 (Box 41, Folder 923)
        - Louis the Fish, circa 2000-2001 (Box 41, Folder 924)
        - Side by Side, Walker & Company, circa 2000-2001 (Box 41, Folder 925)
        - Side by Side manuscript, circa 2000-2001 (Box 41, Folder 926)
      - Storied City: A Children's Book Walking-Tour Guide to New York City, circa 2001-2003
        - Storied City blad, circa 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 901)
        - Chelsea and Gramercy Park, circa 2001-2003 (Box 41, Folder 902)
        - Midtown Manhattan, circa 2001-2003 (Box 41, Folder 903)
        - West Side, circa 2001-2003 (Box 41, Folder 904)
        - Harlem, circa 2001-2003 (Box 41, Folder 905)
        - Brooklyn, circa 2001-2003 (Box 41, Folder 906)
        - The Bronx, circa 2001-2003 (Box 41, Folder 907)
        - Staten Island, circa 2001-2003 (Box 41, Folder 908)
        - Storied City day trips, circa 2001-2003 (Box 41, Folder 909)
        - Storied City final manuscript (copy edited), circa 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 927-928)
        - New York City book, circa 2001-2003 (Box 42, Folder 929-930)
        - Letters from readers, circa 2003 (Box 42, Folder 931-932)
        - Correspondence and publicity, circa 2003 (Box 42, Folder 933-937)
        - Greenwich Village, circa 2001-2003 (Box 42, Folder 938)
        - East Side, circa 2001-2003 (Box 42, Folder 939)
        - Storied City letters from readers, circa 2003 (Box 42, Folder 940)
        - Storied City permissions copies, circa 2001-2003 (Box 42, Folder 941)
        - Storied City reviews and publicity, circa 2003 (Box 42, Folder 942)
        - Storied City missing things and corrections log, circa 2001-2003 (Box 42, Folder 943-944)
        - Storied City corrections, circa 2001-2003 (Box 42, Folder 945)
        - Lower Manhattan, circa 2001-2003 (Box 42, Folder 946)
        - Storied City bibliography, circa 2001-2003 (Box 42, Folder 947)
        - Other cities, circa 2001-2003 (Box 42, Folder 948)
        - Storied City captions, circa 2001-2003 (Box 42, Folder 949)
        - Queens, circa 2001-2003 (Box 42, Folder 950)
      - The Wand in the Word: Conversations with Writers of Fantasy, circa 2004-2006
        - Cover and photos, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 951)
        - The Wand in the Word correspondence, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 952)
        - The Wand in the Word reviews, circa 2006 (Box 43, Folder 953)
        - The Wand in the Word publicity, circa 2006 (Box 43, Folder 954)
        - Flap copy, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 955)
        - Rights, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 956)
        - Junior Library Guild note, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 957)
        - Conversations with writers of fantasy, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 958-959)
        - The Wand in the Word new information, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 960)
        - Fantasy authors, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 961-962)
        - Lloyd Alexander interview, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 963)
        - Susan Cooper interview, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 964)
        - Fanny Billingsley interview, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 965)
        - Nancy Farmer interview, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 966)
        - Brian Jacques interview, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 967-968)
        - Diana Wynne Jones interview, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 969)
        - Madeleine L'Engle interview, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 970)
        - Ursula K. LeGuin interview, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 971)
        - Garth Nix interview, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 972)
        - Terry Pratchett interview, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 973)
        - Tamora Pierce interview, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 974)
        - Philip Pullman interview, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 975)
        - Jane Yolen interview, circa 2004-2006 (Box 43, Folder 976)
        - The Wand in the Word color layout, 2004 (Box 92 (Oversize), Folder 2300)
        - The Wand in the Word black and white layout, corrected, 2005 (Box 92 (Oversize), Folder 2301)
    - Short Works, circa 1981-2015
      Documents the research, writing, and publication of Marcus's short works, including articles, forewords, and talks. Includes research materials, notes, drafts, correspondence, publicity, and clippings. A significant portion of the materials concerns Marcus's tenure as contributing editor and children's literature reviewer at Parenting magazine, circa 1987-2008. Note that a significant portion of Marcus's research materials consists of duplicates of archival materials held by other libraries. Where possible, the institution holding the originals has been noted. Inquiries about originals of these materials should be directed to the holding institution.
      Organized into three subseries: Night Kitchen Radio Theater, Parenting Magazine, and Other Short Works and Events.
      - Night Kitchen Radio Theater, circa 2005-2006
        Arranged as received.
        - Night Kitchen Radio Theater, circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 977-979)
        - "Sherlock Holmes and the Golden Tooth", circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 980)
        - "The Fisherman's Wife", circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 981)
        - "The Emperor's New Clothes", circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 982)
        - "Pinocchio", 2006 (Box 44, Folder 983)
        - "The Nose", circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 984)
        - "The End of the Beginning", circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 985)
        - "Clever Bill", circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 986)
        - "The Magician's Boy", circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 987)
        - "The End of the Beginning", 2006 (Box 44, Folder 988)
        - "Bread and Roses, Too", circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 989)
        - "Seek", circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 990-991)
        - "Hey, Al", circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 992)
        - Library of Congress Federal Theatre Project, circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 993)
        - "Harry and Lulu", 2006 (Box 44, Folder 994)
        - Leonard Marcus, Night Kitchen Radio Theater, circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 995)
        - Night Kitchen Radio Theater, Random House sales conference, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 996)
        - Night Kitchen Radio Theater, Listen Up!, circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 997)
        - New Night Kitchen Radio Theater, circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 998)
        - "Bad Boy", circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 999)
        - "Bread and Roses, Too", circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 1000)
        - Henry Street Series, Kafka's The Metamorphosis, circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 1001)
        - Night Kitchen Radio Theater correspondence, circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 1002)
        - "Bad Boy", circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 1003)
        - "Lysistrata", circa 2005-2006 (Box 44, Folder 1004-1005)
      - Parenting Magazine, circa 1987-2008
        - February 2006 reviews (Box 37, Folder 823)
        - March 2006 reviews (Box 37, Folder 824)
        - April 2006 reviews (Box 37, Folder 825)
        - May 2006 reviews (Box 37, Folder 826)
        - June 2006 reviews (Box 37, Folder 827)
        - July 2006 reviews (Box 37, Folder 828)
        - August 2006 reviews (Box 37, Folder 829)
        - September 2006 reviews (Box 37, Folder 830)
        - October 2006 reviews (Box 37, Folder 831)
        - November 2006 reviews (Box 37, Folder 832)
        - Parenting Best Books Awards, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 833)
        - February-June 2007 reviews (Box 37, Folder 834)
        - July-November 2007 reviews (Box 37, Folder 835)
        - Parenting Best Books Awards, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 836)
        - February-June 2008 reviews (Box 37, Folder 837)
        - July-December 2008 reviews (Box 37, Folder 838)
        - Short takes, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 1016)
        - Parenting first column, circa 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 1017)
        - Parenting second column, circa 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 1018)
        - Parenting third column, circa 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 1019)
        - Parenting fourth column, circa 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 1020)
        - Parenting contracts and letterheads, circa 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 1021)
        - Parenting, "Care & Feeding: Christmas and Hanukkah Books", circa 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 1022)
        - Parenting book bag reviews, circa 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 1023)
        - Parenting sidebar: books on arrival of a new brother or sister, circa 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 1024)
        - Parenting, American Booksellers Association, Anaheim California, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 1025)
        - Parenting best books, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 1026)
        - Parenting Reading Magic Awards, 1988 (Box 45, Folder 1027)
        - Parenting ninth column, circa 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1028)
        - Parenting tenth column, circa 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1029)
        - Parenting eleventh column, circa 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1030)
        - Parenting twelfth column, circa 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1031)
        - Parenting thirteenth column, circa 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1032)
        - Parenting fourteenth column, circa 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1033)
        - Parenting fifteenth column, circa 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1034)
        - Parenting sixteenth column, circa 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1035)
        - Parenting seventeenth column, circa 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1036)
        - Parenting eighteenth column, circa 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1037)
        - Parenting nineteenth column, circa 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1038)
        - Parenting twenty-first column, circa 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1039)
        - Parenting twenty-second column, circa 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1040)
        - Parenting twenty-third column, circa 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1041)
        - Parenting twenty-fourth column, circa 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1042)
        - Parenting twenty-fifth column, circa 1987-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1043)
        - Parenting Reading Magic Awards, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 1044)
        - February 1998 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1045)
        - Avi sidebar, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 1046)
        - March 1998 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1047)
        - April 1998 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1048)
        - May 1998 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1049)
        - June/July 1998 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1050)
        - Book Expo America, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 1051)
        - June/July 1998 books on tape (Box 45, Folder 1052)
        - Parenting newsletter reading list, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 1053)
        - American Library Association conference, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 1054)
        - August 1998 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1055)
        - September 1998 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1056)
        - October 1998 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1057)
        - November 1998 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1058)
        - February 1999 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1059)
        - Parenting Rosa Parks interview, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 1060)
        - American Booksellers Association, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 1061)
        - February 1996 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1062)
        - March 1996 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1063)
        - April 1996 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1064)
        - May 1996 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1065)
        - Reading Magic Awards, 1998, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 1066)
        - June/July 1996 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1067)
        - August 1996 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1068)
        - September 1996 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1069)
        - Reading timeline, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 1070)
        - October 1996 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1071)
        - November 1996 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1072)
        - Reading Magic Awards, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 1073)
        - December 1996/January 1997 audio reviews (Box 45, Folder 1074)
        - Book club proposal material, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 1075)
        - February 1997 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1076)
        - March 1997 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1077)
        - April 1997 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1078)
        - 10 leaders piece, 1997 (Box 45, Folder 1079)
        - May 1997 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1080)
        - June/July 1997 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1081)
        - August 1997 reviews (Box 45, Folder 1082)
        - Book Expo America, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 1083)
        - September 1997 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1084)
        - October 1997 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1085)
        - Books on tape/authors on web, 1997 (Box 46, Folder 1086)
        - November 1997 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1087)
        - December 1997/January 1998 reviews, 1997-1998 (Box 46, Folder 1088)
        - Best of 10 reviews, 1998-1999 (Box 46, Folder 1089)
        - Parenting newsletter, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 1090)
        - Custom Publishing reading list, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 1091)
        - March 1999 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1092)
        - Bible stories sidebar, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 1093)
        - April 1999 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1094)
        - May 1999 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1095)
        - June/July 1999 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1096)
        - August 1999 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1097)
        - September 1999 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1098)
        - October 1999 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1099)
        - November 1999 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1100)
        - 11th issue book reviews, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 1101)
        - Reading Magic Awards, 1999 (Box 46, Folder 1102)
        - February 2000 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1103)
        - March 2000 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1104)
        - Poetry sidebar, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 1105)
        - April 2000 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1106)
        - May 2000 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1107)
        - June/July 2000 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1108)
        - August 2000 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1109)
        - Kevin Henkes interview, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 1110)
        - September 2000 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1111)
        - Fall 2000 sidebars (Box 46, Folder 1112)
        - October 2000 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1113)
        - Toyota reading list, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 1114)
        - November 2000 reviews (Box 46, Folder 1115)
        - Author websites, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 1116)
        - 11th issue, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 1117)
        - Parenting family book, 2000 (Box 46, Folder 1118)